Maurice B. Waters 3271 E. Flamingo Rd Apt 103 Paradise, NV 89121 973.432.5625 NJDiesel@yahoo.com

SUMMARY:

Highly experienced, motivated, organized, personable and creative corporate sales professional with the proven ability to generate new business and thoroughly penetrate and retain existing accounts in a fast paced environment with minimum supervision. Excellent verbal, written, listening, problem solving and negotiation skills. Comfortable interacting and delivering presentations with C-level executives and the consumer. Excellent prospecting, closing and customer service skills.

EXPERIENCE:

HelloFresh, Linden, NJ

May 2016 - May 2017

Customer Retention Account Executive

- Contract position where the primary responsibility was to provide customer retention.
- Provided customer service in a heavy inbound call center environment
- Provided instruction on how to more efficiently use the HelloFresh online software.

Time Warner Cable, New York, NY

Dec 2014 - May 2016

- Concierge Account Executive
 - Managed up to 25 buildings gaining access to these buildings to sell internet, phone & other cloud based products.
 - Position required developing relationships with property owners, co-op boards, leasing agents, real estate developer's contractors & superintendents to generate new business through referrals & maintain existing accounts.
 - Provided a higher level of customer service to the end user than previously available to ensure customer retention.

CreditRiskMonitor, Valley Cottage, NY

May 2012 - Oct 2014

Account Executive

- Generated new business by placing 80 100 outbound cold calls per day.
- Performed online product demonstrations for C-level executives (SaaS).
- Researched & provided needs analysis on prospective clients.
- Exceptional closing ratio.

Web Access Newark, NJ

Dec 2008 - Nov 2011

Regional Account Executive/Channel Account Manager

- generated new business through cold calling, professional networking & other methods.
- thoroughly penetrated & provided customer service for existing accounts.
- Responsible for sales in the northeast region.
- Delivered C-level presentations at trade shows & at customer sites.

Troi.Net, Staten Island, NY

Oct 2006 - Dec 2008

Senior Account Executive

- Generated new business through cold calling, canvassing, email & professional networking.
- maintained existing accounts for our professional design, development, maintenance & managed services group.
- provided sales training for field engineers.
- Delivered C-level presentations.

New Horizons Computer Learning Center

Aug 2004 - Sept 2006

Account Executive

- generated new business through cold calling & canvassing.
- provided customer service for existing accounts to ensure customer retention.

- thoroughly penetrated assigned accounts.
- Determined current and future customer needs via periodic on site visits.

Micro Warehouse Lakewood, NJ

March 2002 - May 2004

Sales Engineer

- Responsible for prospecting & qualifying new business.
- completely penetrated existing accounts and regularly interfaced with point of contact to maintain existing clients & generate referrals.
- increased the overall sales of networking products by 3 percent per month.
- Responsible for relieving a quota of \$175,000 in GP per month.
- provided consulting services to clients at the beginning of their project cycles.
- Provided customers with system configurations, router selections, and VPN/security solutions & networking product comparisons.
- Researched & selected wireless & storage solutions based on the features & functionality requirements of the end
 user.
- Managed & provided technical training for my team of 25 inside sales reps.
- Prepared & delivered engaging product presentations, showing the value add of doing business with Micro Warehouse.
- actively engaged in on-going product, technical, systems and sales training.
- 50 to 75 percent above quota every month.

SAVVIS Communications New York City, NY

Jun 1999 - Sept 2001

Global Account Manager

- Evaluated end users existing wide area connection technologies.
- recommended any of the following technologies to accomplish the end users goals (ATM, Frame Relay, Intelligent IP, VPN, OC-X, Hosting or some form of integrated access).
- Responsible for establishing new business relationships within & outside the financial community.
- thoroughly penetrated existing accounts.
- Consistently 25 to 50 percent above quota.
- Delivered C-level presentations at customer sites & trade shows.

CCS Technologies, Inc. New York City, NY

Nov 1993 - Dec 1998

Senior Account Manager/Network Architect

- Established new business relationships through extensive cold calling, canvassing & professional networking.
- Maintained & developed 75 100 existing accounts for Novell Platinum systems integrator & Microsoft Solutions
 Provider with a strong emphasis on customer retention through regular contact, needs analysis & future goals.
- Determined bandwidth requirements & selected & sold wide area circuits utilizing providers such as Qwest, Global Crossing, Broadwing, PSInet, MCI WorldCom & others.
- Consistently 50 to 100 percent above quota.
- Implemented document Management/Imaging and Workflow solutions.
- Rendered hardware and software support services for the corporate end user & prepared needs assessments.
- Recommend e-mail systems, Internet & remote access methods.
- Determined proper configuration for communications and applications servers & mini/mainframe integration.

EDUCATION:

Essex County College, Newark, NJ

Associates of Arts & Science Major: Engineering Technology

New Jersey Institute of Technology, Newark, NJ

Bachelor of Science Major: Engineering Technology

Professional Certifications:

Certified Cisco Sales Expert, Comp TIA A+, Certified NetWare Sales Professional, HP/COMPAQ Networking Sales training, Cisco Voice Video & Data Integration, Cisco VoIP, 3Com Layer 3 and Layer 4 Switching, Check Point, Novell Group Wise. SUN Workgroup, Enterprise, Interoperability & Server Consolidation. SUN E10K and A7000 sales training. HP SAN solutions training, Windows 95/98, 2000, XP Pro, 7, 10 & MS Office Suite